Guide to the Robert Hebb Records
Cary Institute of Ecosystem Studies
Robert Hebb Records
1970 - 1984
1974 - 1983
This collection contains folders of the administrative materials of Robert Hebb, Director of Horticulture at the Cary Arboretum from 1974 to 1984.
10 linear feet (23 boxes)
Hebb, Robert S.
Cary Institute of Ecosystem Studies PO Box AB Millbrook, NY 12545-0129 845-677-7600 x164
This collection is open to researchers by appointment only.
Robert Hebb received a degree in ornamental horticulture from the University of Rhode Island in 1965, after which he worked as a student gardener at the Royal Botanical Gardens, Kew in England until 1968. From 1968 to 1974, Hebb worked at the Arnold Arboretum of Harvard University, where he was the Assistant Horticulturist. He became the Director of Horticulture at the Cary Arboretum in 1974, when the arboretum was under the management of the New York Botanical Garden.
Cary Arboretum; correspondence; Arboretums; Horticulture; New York Botanical Garden; field notes; Dutchess (N.Y.); Millbrook (N.Y.)
This collection consists largely of memoranda, correspondence, and inventories of plant material. Some landscape and building plans, photographs, and miscellaneous newspaper articles and pamphlets are also included. The correspondence is mostly communication with administrators and employees about operations and finances. A large amount of correspondence with arboreta, other horticulturists, and garden clubs about plant inventories, seed exchange, and events is also present. The collection is divided into 10 series with 510 folders, a number of which contain only one or two items. Materials such as field books and survey sheets that are not in folders can be found in Series 5. Additional folders originally in the collection were given to the New York Botanical Garden.
- 1 - Correspondence, 1970 - 1984; 1974 - 1983
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains correspondence, memoranda, and a few miscellaneous items such as plant lists, newspaper articles, pamphlets, and maps that were sent alongside the correspondence. A few folders contain correspondence dated before 1974 that pertains to Hebb’s employment at the Arnold Arboretum.
  - A - General Correspondence, 1975 - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Janet, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ames, Ned, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Applebaum, Bruce, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Armstrong, Gregory, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Asherman, Karen, 1978 - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Asherman, Karen - Native Plant Survey, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - B - General Correspondence, 1975 - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Barnes, Lee, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bartlett Arboretum, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bartow-Pell Mansion, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Beal, Bill, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Behnke, Frances, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Belanger, Jacques, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bemis, Royall, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bentley, Edward S., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Blackburn, Benjamin, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Blank, Joseph, 1975 - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Blodgett, Stephen, 1979 - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bodwell, Mary, 1976 - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bookman, George, 1974 - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Boutard, Ray, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bouton, John, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bristol, Peter, 1976 - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Brotherton, Jim, 1976 - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Dan, 1974 - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Brown, Dan - Greenhouse & Nursery, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Brown, Dick, 1975 - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bruckmann, Donald J., 1977 - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Buchter, Tom, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - C - General Correspondence, 1976 - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Cabot, F. H., 1974 - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Caccamo, Mrs. Anthony, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Castro, Nash, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Chase, Dr. Sherret S., 1976 - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Christie, Liz, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Clausen, Ruth, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Cook, Robert E., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Coon, Nelson, 1975 - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Corning, Mrs. Erastus II, 1976 - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Cote, Leonard J., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Crammond, Ann, 1980 - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Creech, John, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Crossman, Muriel, 1975 - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Crovello, T. J., 1977 - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - D - General Correspondence, 1972 - 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Dann, Elliot W., 1980 - 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Deer Hill Conference & Retreat Center, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Delafield, John W., 1979 - 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Delendick, Thomas J., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - DeWolf, Gordon P., Jr., 1979 - 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Diaconescu, Floritza, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Diem, Kenneth L., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dirr, Michael A., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Dudley, Theodore, 1980 - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Dumaine, Susan, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Dykeman, Peter, 1975 - 1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dyson, Charles H., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - E - General Correspondence, 1977 - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Eberstadt, Frederick, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Eisenstadter, Ingrid, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Elias, T. - Research Programs, 1974 - 1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Engle, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Erskine, C. M., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Estey, Dr. Edith, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Everitt, T. - Encyclopedia, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Exton, William, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - F - General Correspondence, 1975 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Faust, Sara, 1980 - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Ferrinea, V., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Fish, H., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Fliegner, Hans J., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Foster, H. Lincoln, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Frowine, Steven, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Frunze Botanical Garden, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Fuller, Henry, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - G - General Correspondence, 1974 - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Garden Club of America, 1975 - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Garden Club of New Jersey, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Garden Clubs - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1978 - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Gardner, Lola & Ben, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Gerhold, Prof. Henry, 1975 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Gherardi, Mrs. Walter R., 1980 - 1981 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Goldsmith, Bill, 1975 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Goodland, Robert, 1975 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Gossler, Roger, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Goudy, David, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Green, James - Lagerstroemia, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Gussin, Arnold, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - H - General Correspondence, 1975 - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hara, Prof. Hiroshi, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Heins, Esther, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Heller, Mr. William B., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Hester, Dr. James M., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Hicklin, Wayne & Margaret, 1978 - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Hicks, Jennifer, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Hill, Mrs. Julian, 1976 - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Hillier, 1975 - 1977 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Holmgren, Patricia K., 1974 - 1975 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Holweg, Arthur W., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Horn, Axel, 1975 - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Howard, Dr. Richard A., 1975 - 1976 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Hoxie, Lynn, 1978 - 1979 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Hoyt, Harold, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Hubbard, Fred H., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Iltis, Hugh, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - International Paper Company, 1977 - 1978 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Irwin, Howard, 1975 - 1978 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Iseli, Jean, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Iverson, Richard, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Jones, Clive, 1980 - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Jurkowski, Al, 1980 - 1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - K - General Correspondence, 1974 - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Karnosky, Dave, 1975 - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Keller, Alton, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Kemble, William (Bedford Oak), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy, James S., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Kitchawan Research Laboratory, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Klehm, Roy, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Koller, Gary, 1975 - 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Koster, Ronald A., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Krieg, Henry A., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Krukoff, B. A., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - L - General Correspondence, 1975 - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Lancaster, Roy, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Lape, Fred, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Lapin, Pyotr, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Las Cruces Botanical Garden, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Lasher, Robert, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Lasker Foundation, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Lavin, Chuck, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Lees, C. B., 1975 - 1978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Levy, Ira H., 1980 - 1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Lighty, Richard W., 1976 - 1983 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Logee’s, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Long, C. Robert, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Longland, David, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - LoPresti, Philip J., undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Lord & Burnham, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Lovelace House - Rehabilitation Project, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - M - General Correspondence, 1975 - 1983 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Mate, Zoltan (International Paper Company), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Mazzeo, Peter M., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - McAninch, J., 1977 - 1982 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - McChesney, James, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - McDaniel, Dr. Joseph C., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - McGourty, Fred, 1976 - 1982 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Menucci, Daniel W., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Mickel, John, 1977 - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Miller, Carl Ferris, 1976 - 1977 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Mohonk Mountain House, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Mooney, Harold, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Morse, Herbert C., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Munk, Bill, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - N - General Correspondence, 1976 - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - New England Wild Flower Society, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Nickou, N., 1977 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Nitzelius, Tor, 1971 - 1975 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Norweb, R. Henry, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Numrich, Francis, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - O - General Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Oakes, Walter W., 1979 - 1980 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - O'Brien, Sally, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Ode, Arthur H., 1977 - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - P - General Correspondence, 1974 - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Payne, W. W., 1977 - 1983 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Pennsylvania Horticultural Society, 1976 - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Pepper, Jane (Longwood Student), 1975 - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Plummer, Jean, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Potter, Basil C., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Prance, Dr. Ian, 1975 - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Prince, Martha, 1976 - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Quinlan, Robert, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - R - General Correspondence, 1976 - 1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Rausch, Geoffrey, 1975 - 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Rogers, Owen, 1980 - 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - S - General Correspondence, 1974 - 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sales, John, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Santamour, Frank, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Schnall, Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Schubert, Winfried, 1975 - 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Seeger, Pete, 1977 - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Setliff, Ed, 1975 - 1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Shaw, Dick, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Shoumatoff, N., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Simmons, John, 1975 - 1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Smalley, Tim, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Somers, G. Fred, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Spring, John J., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Stevenson, James, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Sturges, Paul, 1976 - 1977 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Suk, Carl W., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Swain, Roger, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Swenson, Allan A., 1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - T - General Correspondence, 1975 - 1979 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Taylor, C. Powers, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Tillman, Gus, 1975 - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Totemeier, Carl A., 1981 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - V - General Correspondence, 1975 - 1981 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Van Alstine, Ken, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Vermeulen, John & Son, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Viette, Andre, 1981 - 1982 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - W - General Correspondence, 1974 - 1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Wagner, J. - Storch Associates, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Welles, Halsted S., 1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Wheaton, Steven, 1976 - 1979 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Woodwell, George, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Wright, Russell, 1973 - 1975 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Wyman, D., 1977 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- 2 - Administrative Materials, 1973 - 1984; 1974 - 1983
  This series contains memoranda, other correspondence, building plans and maps, and a few miscellaneous items such as pamphlets, newspaper articles, and plant lists.
  - AABGA - Autumn 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - AABGA - Autumn 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - AABGA - Regional Meetings - Procedures, 1977 - 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - AABGA - National Meeting - Photos, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - AABGA - 1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - AAM - Accreditation, 1981 - 1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Accession System, 1974 - 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Aerial Surveys, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Albert Einstein College - Greenhouse Rental, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - America's Garden Book - Revision, 1977 - 1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - American Nurseryman, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - American Rock Garden Society - 1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report - Horticulture - 1974-75, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report - Horticulture - 1975-76, 1975 - 1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report - Horticulture - 1976-79, 1977 - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Arnold Arboretum - Japan/Korea 1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Bacon Flats Lodge, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bio-Fert, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Boston - Tour, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bronx River Restoration Project, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cary Arboretum - Accessions, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Cary Arboretum - Power Lines, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Cary Arboretum - Time Records, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Casoron Damage - Scots Pine, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Catalpa x Chilopsis Hybrid, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Census of Agriculture - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Central Park, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Central Park Pinetum - Arthur Ross, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - CETA, 1977 - 1978 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Chemical Usage Committee, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Chinese Seed Exchange - Peking, 1974 - 1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Chinese Seeds - Nanking, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Christmas Tree Display - 1981 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - CIAO - Committee on Internal Arboretum Operations, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Collections - Questionnaire, 1973 - 1974 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Computer - SECOS, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Container Exhibit - Text, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Container Project - Adminis. Matters, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Crear House - "Bee House", 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cross Country Skiing, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Director - Cary Arboretum Search Committee, 1976 - 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Drought Damage Report - 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Dutchess Day School - Auctions, 1977 - 1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Energy Conference, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Seed Producers, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - European American Bank Atrium, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Fall-For-All 1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Firewood, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Gifford House, 1976 - 1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Gifford House - Site Plan, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Gravel Sites, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Greenhouse - Alarm System, 1974 - 1977 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Greenhouse - Barn, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Greenhouse - Bench Layout, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Greenhouse - Boiler Problem, 1974 - 1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Greenhouse - Cold Storage House, 1975 - 1977 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Greenhouse - Cooling Switches, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Greenhouse - Educational Displays, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Greenhouse - Electrical Needs, 1975 - 1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Greenhouse - Emergency Procedures, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Greenhouse - Fan & Pad System, 1976 - 1977 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Greenhouse - General, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Greenhouse - Headhouse Alterations, 1973 - 1978 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Greenhouse - Hydrant, 1974 - 1976 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Greenhouse - Lath House, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Greenhouse - Memoranda, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Greenhouse - Mihan's Instructions, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Greenhouse - Nursery Certification & Purchase Permit, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Greenhouse - Nursery Inspections Reports, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Greenhouse - Parking Lot Layout, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Greenhouse - Peninsula Bench System, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Greenhouse - Plastic Covering, 1977 - 1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Greenhouse - Progress Report, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Greenhouse - Propagation Program, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Greenhouse - Road Paving, 1975 - 1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Greenhouse - Security Checks, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Greenhouse - Soil Mixtures, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Greenhouse - Supplies Ordered, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Greenhouse - Temperature Records, 1973 - 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Greenhouse - Turbulator Fans, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Greenhouse - Weekend & Holiday Schedules, 1979 - 1981 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Grid System - EDM Equipment, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Grid System - Estimates, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Grid System - Map, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Grid System - Supplies, 1976 - 1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Hemlock Forest - NYBG, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Henry House, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Herbarium - Cary Arboretum, 1975 - 1978 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Horticultural Society of NY, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Horticulture Policy Committee, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Horticulture Policy Committee Report 1980 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Hortus Club, 1975 - 1981 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Hortus III, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Hustler Mower, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Hydroseeding Gravel Bank, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - IBM, 1976 - 1983 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Institute for Urban Horticulture, 1981 - 1982 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Institute of Ecology, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Insurance Policies, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - International Paper Company - Greenhouse Rental, 1977 - 1978 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Interoffice Correspondence - General, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Inventory - Horticulture, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Job Applicants, 1975 - 1976 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Job Descriptions - Horticultural Positions, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Kew Conference - Sept. 1975, 1975 - 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Kew Legume Conference - 1978, 1975 - 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Kitchawan Research Lab, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Label Information, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Landscape Critics Council, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Landscape Critics Council (2), 1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Lath House - Cary Arboretum, 1973 - 1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Lectures, Old, 1974 - 1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Legume Project - G. T. Prance, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Library - NYBG, 1974 - 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Library Requests, 1974 - 1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Living Collections - Plans, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Lord & Burnham, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Maintenance Center, 1975 - 1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Major Tree Avenue, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Maps - Cary Arboretum, 1974 - 1975 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Massachusetts Horticultural Congress - 1978, 1977 - 1978 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Massachusetts Horticultural Society Show - 1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Master Plan - Cary Arboretum, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Master Plan - Horticulture Department - 1st Draft, 1975 - 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Methane Plant, 1980 - 1982 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Natural Heritage Trust, 1978 - 1982 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Nursery - Progress Report, 1980 - 1983 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - NYBG - School of Horticulture - Plant Lists, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Onteora Arboretum, 1978 - 1983 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Peer Review Committee - 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Peking Botanical Garden, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Pesticide Applicators - Registration, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Pesticide Permits, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Pesticide/Herbicide Use - 1980, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Philadelphia Flower Show - Judging, 1977 - 1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Plant Science Building, 1975 - 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Plant Science Building (2), 1974 - 1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Plant Science Building - Courtyard Plans, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Plant Science Building - Greenhouse, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Plant Science Building - Landscape Plans, 1975 - 1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Plant Science Building - Research Greenhouse, 1975 - 1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Plantings - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Plants to Obtain - Nursery Sources, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Progress Reports - Greenhouse, 1975 - 1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Progress Reports - J. Blank, 1974 - 1975 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Progress Reports - Nursery, 1974 - 1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Progress Reports - Surveying, 1974 - 1975 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Purchase College - Internships, 1975 - 1976 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Purchase College - Seminars, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Purchase College - Student Evaluations, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Rhododendron Conference - International Nomenclature, 1976 - 1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Rosedale Nurseries, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Royal Botanic Gardens - Sydney, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Sasaki Associates - Consulting, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - School of Horticulture - Advisory Committee Minutes, 1979 - 1983 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - School of Horticulture - Bronx Community College Proposal, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - School of Horticulture - Field Trips, 1979 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - School of Horticulture - NYBG, 1977 - 1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - School of Horticulture - Plant Lists, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - School of Horticulture - Schedule - 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - School of Horticulture - 1981, 1980 - 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Seedlings, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Seniority Lists - Union, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Sharon Turnpike - Tree Work, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Spare Plants List, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Spring Party - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Stream Bank Stabilization Project, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Syracuse - Plant Propagation Project, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Target Rock Wildlife Refuge, 1980 - 1981 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Telephone Call Survey, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Vassar College, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Vegetable Garden Demo - 1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Visitor Center - Plans, 1975 - 1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Volunteers, 1975 - 1976 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - VWR Scientific Proposal, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Weather Stations, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Weed Day - 1977 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Woodlot Management Program, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - YCC Program, 1979 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - YCC Program - 1981, 1980 - 1981 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - YETP Program, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- 3 - Miscellaneous, 1972 - 1982
  This series contains miscellaneous memoranda, correspondence, and other administrative materials.
  - Publications, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Rhododendron Dell Committee, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Hoyt, Harold, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Applebaum, Bruce, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Greenhouse Work Schedule, 1980 - 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Alex Pearl - Vassar College, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)